

# PABLO BRANCOLI

#### Software Engineer | Data Scientist

- pbrancoli@uc.cl
- **J** +569 79873658
- Santiago, Chile
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/pablo-brancoli-0aa8191b7/
- **PORTFOLIO** https://github.com/Brocoleta

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

# **ABOUT ME**

Python

**Typescript** 

Google Cloud

ML Python

**AWS** 

Deep Learning

React

Firebase

Power BI

Excel

Civil Engineer specialized in Computer Science and with a focus on Data Science, passionate about providing efficient solutions through the use of advanced technologies and applying knowledge of Machine Learning and Data Science.

### **EDUCATION**

Civil Engineering in Computer Science with specialization in Data Science | Pontifical Catholic University of Chile

**1** 03/2018 - 07/2023

Santiago, Chile

### INTERESTS

Artificial Intelligence

Open Al

Camping

Trekking

Football

Physics

High School Education | San Benito School

**1** 04/2004 - 12/2017

Santiago, Chile

# LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native **English: Advanced** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Developer and Data Scientist | Sundes Collection

**1** 04/2021 - 07/2023

Santiago, Chile

- Worked on cloud development projects using Google Cloud Platform and Firebase, achieving timely and efficient deliveries.
- Designed and implemented a Machine Learning model to predict house prices.

#### Scout Leader | Santiago Scout Group

**=** 04/2018 - 07/2021

- Santiago, Chile
- Managed and supervised the finances of a 200-member scout group, optimizing resources and ensuring participation in key events.

#### **PROJECTS**

Data Science Portfolio



 Portfolio of Data Science/Engineer applications, using AWS services such as S3, EC2, LAMBDA, ATHENA, and others like Apache Airflow or SnowFlake. More information in the repository's readme: https://github.com/Brocoleta/Brocoleta

#### 



• Conducted a study on targeted attacks on recommendation systems, biasing their results in favor or against certain elements. The link to the document is available in the repository.